Aleksandr Gerasimenko

Male, 24 years, born on 7 June 1995

+86 (188) 42416253
gera-alex@mail.ru
— preferred means of communication

Reside in: China, Guangzhou

Citizenship: Russia, work permit at: Russia, China

Willing to relocate, ready for business trips



Work experience

November 2017 — till now

South China Service Group, Guangzhou, China

Network Engineer

This position involves: CISCO, Mikrotik routing traffic by using BGP, OSPF, RIP, administrating and security Linux/Windows servers, UPS support, LAN/WLAN configuration, routing with L2/L3 control and uncontrol switchers. Configuration GPO, SAMBA, DFS, DNS. For avoiding the Great Firewall by VPN based on OpenVPN, StrongSwan, L2TP/IPSec protocols. Servers virtualization by KVM. Using monitoring system such as Atlassian Jira, Zabbix, NetFlow. Backup and installing/uninstalling by Ansible. Development and support LAMP web-server. Keeping records of equipment, repair or replacement of components.

January 2016 — August 2017

Shenyang heavy mining machinery company, Shenyang, China

Freelancer. Inspecting for programming codes of lathe machines.

This position includes reviewing of mathematic algorithms and measurements in C-program language.

October 2013 — July 2016

Hospital MVD

System administrator

This position involves: server UPS support, administrating server Windows 2012 R2 (AD, SAMBA, RAID) and LAN/WLAN configuration. Routing with using CISCO route, L2 uncontrolled switcher. Development and support of the hospital website. Keeping records of equipment, repair or replacement of components.

October 2012 — September 2013

Fareast Communication Systems

Assistant system administrator

This position includes working in a fast pace information communication company as a personal assistant to the system administrator located in the Russia, which includes installation of structured cabling system, monitoring and analysis of working networks in the city.

Projects	
2019	Commercial project VPN based on OpenVPN and L2TP/IPsec protocols on VPS (bash)
2019	Sensor alarm system in office based on microprocessor ATmega (C++)
2018	Developing a neural network based proactive data protection system in VANETs (Python, TensorFlow
2016	Developing hardware and software complex of data interception in networks by standard 802.11
	b/g/n (degree project)
2016	Developing traffic analyzer of networks by standard 802.11 b/g/n (C++)
2015	Deployment local logging information system of patients in the hospital

Education

2018 Shenyang Aerospace university

Master degree

Computer science and technology (VANET security)

2016 Amur State university

Bachelor degree

Mathematic and information (Information system and technology)

Key skills

Languages Russian — Native

English — I am a fluent speaker

Chinese — HSK 3

Skills C/C++ Python Bash Git Zabbix VPS/AWS TCP/IP Routing LAN/WLAN IT Security

VPN L2TP/IPsec Asterisk Docker Ansible Windows Server 2008 R2 CentOS 7 KVM

CISCO Mikrotik

Additional information

About me

I am very passionate about work, I strive to learn quickly and adapt to these conditions to achieve this goal. I have practical experience in the IT-Department, and I believe that skills will be a good resource for the company. Passionate researcher, and ready to do everything possible to make you not disappointed